<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Newsletters on Tridactyl - a vim-like Firefox WebExtension</title>
    <link>https://tridactyl.xyz/newsletters/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Newsletters on Tridactyl - a vim-like Firefox WebExtension</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 13:14:59 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tridactyl.xyz/newsletters/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Summer 2021</title>
      <link>https://tridactyl.xyz/newsletters/08-summer-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 13:14:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tridactyl.xyz/newsletters/08-summer-2021/</guid>
      <description>Hello,
Welcome to the eighth quarterly Tridactyl newsletter. This one&amp;rsquo;s a bit shorter than usual as I had some consulting work and there&amp;rsquo;s been less time since the previous newsletter. I&amp;rsquo;m trying to catch up and release the newsletters in the (northern hemisphere) seasons that they&amp;rsquo;re named after.
Highlighted new features&amp;nbsp;¶ The big new feature this time is one that people have been asking for for a long time: Tridactyl now has a superignore setting that almost entirely disables Tridactyl after a page reload.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring 2021</title>
      <link>https://tridactyl.xyz/newsletters/07-spring-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 13:46:06 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tridactyl.xyz/newsletters/07-spring-2021/</guid>
      <description>Hello,
Welcome to the seventh quarterly Tridactyl newsletter. Somehow I missed the quarter and it&amp;rsquo;s now summer &amp;hellip; sorry! We added a few neat features this quarter - I find myself using :tabaudio a lot - but most of the work went on changes to our build system which have made working on Tridactyl vastly more pleasurable.
Highlighted new features&amp;nbsp;¶ We have a couple of new features for tab/window management. The first relates to tabs playing audio: :tabaudio, bound to ga by default takes you to the tab currently playing audio in your current window; and a little speaker is shown next to tabs playing audio on :tab completions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winter 2021</title>
      <link>https://tridactyl.xyz/newsletters/06-winter-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 19:26:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tridactyl.xyz/newsletters/06-winter-2021/</guid>
      <description>Hello,
Welcome to the sixth quarterly Tridactyl newsletter. As a gentle reminder, the second (and first paywalled) Tridactyl top-tips newsletter will be going out in the next few days. If you&amp;rsquo;d like to receive it, simply up your monthly pledge to 10 USD or more on GitHub sponsors (preferred, as I get ~30%+ more of your money after taxes and transaction fees) or Patreon. I really appreciate every penny you send - it directly affects how long I can afford to work on Tridactyl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autumn 2020</title>
      <link>https://tridactyl.xyz/newsletters/05-autumn-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 17:40:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tridactyl.xyz/newsletters/05-autumn-2020/</guid>
      <description>Hello,
Welcome to the fifth quarterly Tridactyl newsletter.
We&amp;rsquo;ve had another productive quarter. It hasn&amp;rsquo;t been quite as transformative as the last quarter - the addition of browser-wide &amp;lt;C-,&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;C-6&amp;gt; was hard to beat (I&amp;rsquo;ve personally switched to using &amp;lt;C-,&amp;gt; instead of &amp;lt;Esc&amp;gt; and generally Tridactyl and I get along a lot better :)) - but we have added quite a few nice little things.
Highlighted new features&amp;nbsp;¶ For everyone&amp;nbsp;¶ A few new features relating to completions have been added: &amp;lt;C-o&amp;gt;yy copies the currently selected completion to the clipboard, &amp;lt;S-Delete&amp;gt; executes :tabclose on a selected completion&amp;rsquo;s arguments and &amp;lt;C-Enter&amp;gt; executes the highlighted completion keeping the command line open - particularly useful for, e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer 2020</title>
      <link>https://tridactyl.xyz/newsletters/04-summer-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 13:51:54 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tridactyl.xyz/newsletters/04-summer-2020/</guid>
      <description>Hello,
Welcome to the fourth quarterly Tridactyl newsletter.
We&amp;rsquo;ve got a lot done in the past few months, including some features which people have been asking for for a long time. My personal highlights are:
  &amp;ldquo;passthrough&amp;rdquo; mode, bound to &amp;lt;C-v&amp;gt; in normal mode and &amp;lt;C-o&amp;gt; in ignore mode sends the next keypress or valid keysequence to ignore or normal mode respectively.
  focus-element hint mode, bound to ;;, can now be used to choose which part of the page to scroll - just focus an element contained within that part of the page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winter 2020</title>
      <link>https://tridactyl.xyz/newsletters/02-winter-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 11:24:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tridactyl.xyz/newsletters/02-winter-2020/</guid>
      <description>Hello,
Welcome to the second quarterly Tridactyl newsletter.
Since the last newsletter, we resolved our dispute with the Mozilla add-on reviewers and have been relisted on the AMO. If you like graphs, you can clearly see our time in the wilderness where the AMO did not collect statistics for us here: https://addons.mozilla.org/en-US/firefox/addon/tridactyl-vim/statistics/?last=365
We&amp;rsquo;ve recently added quite a few long-demanded features to the Tridactyl beta, which we&amp;rsquo;ll enumerate in the following paragraphs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autumn 2019</title>
      <link>https://tridactyl.xyz/newsletters/01-autumn-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 11:32:27 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tridactyl.xyz/newsletters/01-autumn-2019/</guid>
      <description>Hi!
It&amp;rsquo;s been an eventful few months for Tridactyl. We were delisted from the AMO and have been slowly trying to get listed again. We&amp;rsquo;re currently waiting to hear back from a reviewer on a query of ours before we submit what we will hope be our final revision which will be accepted. To have a hope of being relisted we have had to do some stuff we didn&amp;rsquo;t want to do, namely editing user.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://tridactyl.xyz/newsletters/tips-and-tricks/1-hint-css-selectors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tridactyl.xyz/newsletters/tips-and-tricks/1-hint-css-selectors/</guid>
      <description>Tridactyl Tips &amp;amp; Tricks 1: Hint mode CSS selectors&amp;nbsp;¶ Hi!
Welcome to the first Tridactyl Tips &amp;amp; Tricks newsletter, as mentioned in the previous Tridactyl newsletter. This newsletter is very experimental so any feedback you have would be appreciated.
This first edition is going out to all sponsors on GitHub and Patreon. Later editions will only go out to sponsors on tiers 10 USD a month and higher; I&amp;rsquo;m trying to raise a bit more revenue since GitHub will no longer double donations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring 2020</title>
      <link>https://tridactyl.xyz/newsletters/03-spring-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tridactyl.xyz/newsletters/03-spring-2020/</guid>
      <description>Hello,
Welcome to the third quarterly Tridactyl newsletter.
It has been an eventful quarter. We received our first payout from GitHub sponsors (it was real, they really did double your donations!). Visual mode has landed in Tridactyl stable. We weren&amp;rsquo;t accepted on to Google Summer of Code. I finally got round to adding a setnull command which lets you remove default settings, e.g. setnull searchurls.google allows you to open google and search for &amp;ldquo;google&amp;rdquo; with your default search engine.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
